http://www.paranormalunderground.net/privacy-statement

HomeSubscribeMagazineAbout UsMagazine ArchiveDigital SubscriptionPrint Copies on DemandTestimonialsSubmissionsAdvertiseLinksContactContact UsPrivacy StatementTerms of ServiceRadioRadio ShowMoreHomeSubscribeMagazineAbout UsMagazine ArchiveDigital SubscriptionPrint Copies on DemandTestimonialsSubmissionsAdvertiseLinksContactContact UsPrivacy StatementTerms of ServiceRadioRadio ShowHomeSubscribeMagazineAdvertiseLinksContactRadio
Privacy Statement
Paranormal Underground is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Paranormal Underground Website and governs data collection and usage. By using the Paranormal Underground website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONParanormal Underground collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or telephone number. Paranormal Underground also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Paranormal Underground. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Website addresses. This information is used by Paranormal Underground for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Paranormal Underground Website.Paranormal Underground encourages you to review the privacy statements of Websites you choose to link to from Paranormal Underground so that you can understand how those Websites collect, use and share your information. Paranormal Underground is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Websites outside of the Paranormal Underground and Paranormal Underground family of Websites.USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONParanormal Underground collects and uses your personal information to operate the Paranormal Underground Website and deliver the services you have requested. Paranormal Underground also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Paranormal Underground and its affiliates if you opt-in to such alerts. Paranormal Underground may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.Paranormal Underground does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Paranormal Underground may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Paranormal Underground may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Paranormal Underground, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Paranormal Underground does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.Paranormal Underground keeps track of pages our customers visit within Paranormal Underground, in order to determine what Paranormal Underground pages are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Paranormal Underground to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.Paranormal Underground Websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Paranormal Underground or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Paranormal Underground; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Paranormal Underground, or the public.USE OF COOKIESThe Paranormal Underground Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Paranormal Underground pages, or register with Paranormal Underground site or services, a cookie helps Paranormal Underground to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Paranormal Underground Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Paranormal Underground features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Paranormal Underground services or Web sites you visit.SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONParanormal Underground secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Paranormal Underground secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENTParanormal Underground will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Paranormal Underground encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Paranormal Underground is protecting your information.CONTACT INFORMATIONParanormal Underground welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Paranormal Underground has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Paranormal Underground at paranormalunderground@live.com.  We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Copyright © 2008-2020 Paranormal Underground® - All Rights Reserved.Privacy StatementTerms of Service
